# George Makasarashvili

**Living:** Georgia

**Date of birth:** 30/11/2001

**Phone number:** (+995) 571706632

Email address: giorgimakasarashvili@gmail.com

**LinkedIn:** https://www.linkedin.com/in/giorgi-makasa/

Website: <a href="https://gio-makasa.github.io">https://gio-makasa.github.io</a>
GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/gio-makasa">https://github.com/gio-makasa</a>
Languages: Georgian(native), English(B2)

I am a student now studying at Caucasus University (3rd year), Computer Science. In terms of Web Development, I have excellent knowledge and experience in HTML, CSS(Sass/Scss), JavaScript (ES6), jQuery, TypeScript, Vue.js. For 2 years I have been working on Fiverr and Upwork as freelancer, mostly editing codes and fixing bugs. In 2023, For 6 months I have been working on projects in Unilab, some of them are already up and running. Also, it's already been 1 year since I started learning vue.js (Vuex) and use it in personal projects. I have a little experience of Angular.

I have working experience of MSSQL and PostgreSQL, I can work with data in Relational Database Management System (RDBMS), create databases and write procedures, also I know Python and I have basic knowledge of Node.js, Java, C, C#, C++, Racket, Algorithms and Data structures.

I am detail-oriented, quick learner, analytical thinker and organized with a high sense of responsibility.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Freelancer – Upwork – front end development (2021-2022)

Freelancer – Fiverr – front end development (2021-2022)

Acceleration Program – Unilab – front end development (2022-2023)

#### **EDUCATION**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery • 2019 • W3schools.com and freecodecamp.com COMPUTER SCIENCE • 2020 - PRESENT • CAUCASUS UNIVERSITY Introduction to Computer Science • 2022 • CS50 • cs50.harvard.edu Vue • 2022 • The Complete Guide (incl. Router & Composition API) • udemy.com

## HARD SKILLS

HTML | CSS | Sass/Scss | Bootstrap 5 | W3.CSS | JavaScript (ES6) | Vue.JS (Vuex) | Angular | TypeScript | JQuery | AJAX | API | JSON | OOP | Git | SQL (MSSQL, PostgreSQL) | Python | Figma

**BASIC**: PHP | Java | React | C/C#/C++ | Racket | Algorithms and Data structures

## **SOFT SKILLS**

Leadership | Collaboration/Teamwork | Time Management | Problem Solving | Critical thinking | Attention to detail | Flexibility/Adaptability | Self Motivated | Accountability | Responsibility | Strong organizational skills